@asphaltcowb0y
Jessica Berman — NWSL Commissioner (since 2022).
The league's Board of Governors (club ownership representatives) controls major decisions.
Michele Kang - Washington Spirit
Spent $30 million+ on women's soccer
Why no answer?
Angie Long - Kansas City Current
Built a $117 million stadium...
...only to let males play
The Wilf Family - Orlando Pride
What excuse will they use?
Money, probably.
NWSL Policy on Transgender Athletes (2021).
Eligibility for transgender women: declare female identity and
keep serum testosterone <10 nmol/L for ≥12 months; compliance is tested.
Suppression can be via medication or surgical castration.
Thousands of young girls...
Is it all about the money?
What happened to women...
Why won't you answer them?